Copyright © 2012 Matthew David Elgert - mdelgert@yahoo.com

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.
 
This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 
You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301  USA 
  
Author: Matthew David Elgert - http://www.codeplex.com/site/users/view/mdelgert

URL: https://cloudbackupscheduler.codeplex.com

Date: 11/16/2012

Name: CloudBackupScheduler.Database

Purpose: 

Dependencies: Visual Studio 2012, .Net Framework 4.5, Microsoft SQL Server 2012

Nuget: 